{
    "questions": [
        {
            "answer": "All of the above",
            "options": [
                "The overall direction taken by the data path",
                "The vertical representation of the average data values",
                "Visual representation of consistency in data",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "question": "A trend in graph represents"
        },
        {
            "answer": "Count",
            "options": [
                "Rate",
                "Frequency",
                "Duration",
                "Count"
            ],
            "question": "Determine the data collection described: Jessa observed her sister hiccup 12 times"
        },
        {
            "answer": "Partial interval",
            "options": [
                "Whole interval",
                "Partial interval",
                "MTS",
                "Frequency"
            ],
            "question": "Describe the measurement procedure: During a 10 second interval, if the client chewed on his hair at any time the therapist would mark this as an occurrence. The therapist is tracking behavior using:"
        },
        {
            "answer": "The client physically has the pencil in his hand",
            "options": [
                "The client begins writing his name",
                "The client begins to move toward opening his pencil case",
                "The client physically has the pencil in his hand",
                "Latency is the incorrect measurement system"
            ],
            "question": "In this particular scenario, latency is being tracked to ensure our client is responding to stimuli in a timely manner. James tells his client, \"Get your pencil so we can write\". James starts his timer, and stops it once"
        },
        {
            "answer": "Assists in the practice of speculations",
            "options": [
                "Helps practitioners optimize effectiveness",
                "Enables practitioners to be accountable to clients, consumers, employers and society",
                "Assists in the practice of speculations",
                "Helps practitioners achieve ethical standards"
            ],
            "question": "As an evidence-based science, there are many reasons to use measurement in reports. Which of these is not true?"
        },
        {
            "answer": "All of the above",
            "options": [
                "Read the data and notes from the last session",
                "Prepare materials needed for the program",
                "Have a clipboard with data sheets or device ready",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "question": "How can therapist prepare for data collection?"
        },
        {
            "answer": "Once the behavior occurs the therapist can move on to the next interval",
            "options": [
                "The environment is altered, therefore the therapist does not need to keep a watchful eye because the end product is visible",
                "Once the behavior occurs the therapist can move on to the next interval",
                "The data overestimates behaviors providing a more accurate representation",
                "The therapist does not need to keep a watchful eye because this measurement procedure does not exist"
            ],
            "question": "One advantage of using Momentary Time Sampling is:"
        },
        {
            "answer": "None of the above",
            "options": [
                "Data",
                "Measurement",
                "Measurement procedures",
                "None of the above"
            ],
            "question": "A trend in graph represents"
        },
        {
            "answer": "An indication that the treatment procedure has moved into a new phase",
            "options": [
                "A temporary disruption from services (winter break, therapist on vacation...)",
                "An indication that the treatment procedure has moved into a new phase",
                "The average values of the data",
                "None of the above"
            ],
            "question": "A solid condition change line indicates:"
        },
        {
            "answer": "Count",
            "options": [
                "Count",
                "Frequency",
                "Latency",
                "Duration"
            ],
            "question": "During a 3 hour session, Jacob observed 7 occurrences of clapping. Which measurement procedure was used?"
        },
        {
            "answer": "Line graph",
            "options": [
                "Pie graph",
                "Bar graph",
                "Cumulative graph",
                "Line graph"
            ],
            "question": "The most common graph used in ABA is:"
        }
    ],
    "questionType": "Second QUIZZ_ Chapter A_ Measurement",
  "questionID" : "2"
  }

  